<resources>
    <string name="stringAppName">BlueCapa</string>
    <string name="stringBleInitTitle">Bluetooth enable</string>
    <string name="stringListActivityTitle">Found devices</string>
    <string name="stringLogListActivityTitle">Log of device activity</string>
    <string name="stringListDeviceTitle">Device options</string>
    <string name="stringSettingsTitle">Settings</string>
    <string name="stringVideoRecordingTitle">Video recording</string>
    <string name="stringActionSettings">Settings</string>
    <string name="stringActionStartScanAddNew">Search for new devices</string>
    <string name="stringActionCleanAndScanNew">Clean current records and search again</string>
    <string name="stringActionShowList">Show advanced list of devices</string>
    <string name="stringActionShowAppAula">Show App EULA</string>
    <string name="stringBleNotSupported">Bluetooth low energy is not supported on this device. Try another one.</string>
    <string name="stringBleEnable">Please enable bluetooth</string>
    <string name="stringFileDialogAudio">Choose file please</string>
    <string name="stringButtonStopScanning">Stop scanning</string>
    <string name="stringButtonGoBack">Go back</string>
    <string name="stringButtonDeleteLogs">Delete logs</string>
    <string name="stringNotificationDisabledSwitch">Notification disabled</string>
    <string name="stringNotificationEnabledSwitch">Notification enabled</string>
    <string name="stringAudioEnabledSwitch">Audio enabled</string>
    <string name="stringAudioDisabledSwitch">Audio disabled</string>
    <string name="stringVibrateEnabledSwitch">Vibration enabled</string>
    <string name="stringVibrateDisabledSwitch">Vibration disabled</string>
    <string name="stringFlashLightEnabledSwitch">Flashlight enabled</string>
    <string name="stringFlashLightDisabledSwitch">Flashlight disabled</string>
    <string name="stringVideoRecordingDisabled">Video recording disabled</string>
    <string name="stringVideoRecordingEnabled">Video recording enabled</string>
    <string name="stringNameEditText">Name</string>
    <string name="stringAudioFile">Audio file</string>
    <string name="stringDeviceOptions">Device options</string>
    <string name="stringChooseMp3">choose mp3</string>
    <string name="stringDeleteAllYesNo">You have decided to delete all devices from list. Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="stringLogsDeleteAllYesNo">You have decided to delete all records from list. Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="stringYes">Yes</string>
    <string name="stringNo">No</string>
    <string name="string_BlueCapEventDetected">BlueCapa event detected</string>
    <string name="stringSettingsNotificationEnabled">Help notifications enabled</string>
    <string name="stringSettingsNotificationDisabled">Help notifications disabled</string>
    <string name="stringCardAdapterCursorException">"couldn't move cursor to position "</string>
    <string name="stringDBM">"dBm, "</string>
    <string name="stringVoltageComma">"V, "</string>
    <string name="stringDevice">"Device "</string>
    <string name="stringX">x</string>
    <string name="stringSelectPicture">Select Picture</string>
    <string name="stringToastBluetoothEnabled">BlueTooth is now Enabled</string>
    <string name="stringToastBluetoothCanceled">Error occurred while enabling.Leaving the application..</string>
    <string name="stringSelectDir">Select directory</string>
    <string name="stringRecordingDisabled">" - video recording disabled"</string>
    <string name="stringRecordingEnabled">" - video recording enabled"</string>
    <string name="stringFlashlightDisabled">" - flashlight disabled"</string>
    <string name="stringFlashlightEnabled">" - flashlight enabled"</string>
    <string name="stringNotificationDisabled">" - notification disabled,\nuse the LONG CLICK to access all time logs of this beacon"</string>
    <string name="stringNotificationEnabled">" - notification enabled,\nuse the LONG CLICK to access all time logs of this beacon"</string>
    <string name="stringVibrationDisabled">" - vibration disabled"</string>
    <string name="stringVibrationEnabled">" - vibration enabled"</string>
    <string name="stringAudioDisabled">" - playing audio disabled,\nuse the LONG CLICK to choose mp3 audio file"</string>
    <string name="stringAudioEnabled">" - playing audio enabled,\nuse the LONG CLICK to choose mp3 audio file"</string>
    <string name="stringStopListenToBeacons">Stopping listen to beacons</string>
    <string name="stringStartListenToBeacons">Starting listen to beacons</string>
    <string name="stringLowPower">Low power</string>
    <string name="stringBalanced">Balanced</string>
    <string name="stringLowLatency">Low latency</string>
    <string name="stringBlueCapService">BlueCapa service</string>
    <string name="stringListenToBeacons">listening to beacons broadcast</string>
    <string name="stringBlueCapServiceRunning">BlueCapa service is running in background</string>
    <string name="stringScanMode">Scan mode</string>
    <string name="stringLowLatencySetting">Low latency</string>
    <string name="string20s">20s</string>
    <string name="stringSettings">Settings</string>
    <string name="stringAudioDuration">Audio duration</string>
    <string name="stringVibrationDuration">Vibration duration</string>
    <string name="string6s">6s</string>
    <string name="stringFlashlightLightDuration">Flashlight light duration</string>
    <string name="string10s">10s</string>
    <string name="stringVideoRecordingDuration">Video recording duration</string>
    <string name="stringDateTime">date time</string>
    <string name="stringVoltage">Voltage</string>
    <string name="stringRssi">Rssi</string>
    <string name="stringMac">Mac</string>
    <string name="stringTitle">Title</string>
    <string name="stringCardPhoto">card photo</string>
    <string name="stringLast">Last</string>
    <string name="string0">0</string>
    <string name="stringIntensity">intensity</string>
    <string name="stringSignal">signal</string>
    <string name="stringBattery">battery</string>
    <string name="stringDelete">delete</string>
    <string name="stringPermissionGranted">Permission is granted to use bluetooth.</string>
    <string name="stringPermissionNotGranted">Permission is not granted so application will not work properly!</string>
    <string name="stringS">s</string>
    <string name="stringNoLogs">no time logs</string>
    <string name="stringChangeTitle">You can change the title with LONG CLICK on it</string>
    <string name="stringChooseNewImage">With LONG CLICK you can choose new image from gallery</string>
    <string name="stringDeleteSwipeIgnore">SHORT CLICK restore all the swiped out cards (ignored beacons)\nLONG CLICK permanently removes all beacons cards</string>
    <string name="stringUpdates"> </string>
    <string name="stringEula">BlueCapa 1.0.0
\nCopyright © 2016 Matej Baran
\n
* END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT *
\n
\nIMPORTANT: PLEASE READ THIS LICENSE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SOFTWARE.
\n
\n1. LICENSE
\n
\nBy receiving, opening the file package, and/or using BlueCapa 1.0.0(\"Software\") containing this software, you agree that this End User User License Agreement(EULA) is a legally binding and valid contract and agree to be bound by it. You agree to abide by the intellectual property laws and all of the terms and conditions of this Agreement.
\n
\nUnless you have a different license agreement signed by Matej Baran your use of BlueCapa 1.0.0 indicates your acceptance of this license agreement and warranty.
\n
\nSubject to the terms of this Agreement, Matej Baran grants to you a limited, non-exclusive, non-transferable license, without right to sub-license, to use BlueCapa 1.0.0 in accordance with this Agreement and any other written agreement with Matej Baran. Matej Baran does not transfer the title of BlueCapa 1.0.0 to you; the license granted to you is not a sale. This agreement is a binding legal agreement between Matej Baran and the purchasers or users of BlueCapa 1.0.0.
\n
\nIf you do not agree to be bound by this agreement, remove BlueCapa 1.0.0 from your computer now and, if applicable, promptly return to Matej Baran by mail any copies of BlueCapa 1.0.0 and related documentation and packaging in your possession.
\n
\n2. DISTRIBUTION
\n
\nBlueCapa 1.0.0 and the license herein granted shall not be copied, shared, distributed, re-sold, offered for re-sale, transferred or sub-licensed in whole or in part except that you may make one copy for archive purposes only. For information about redistribution of BlueCapa 1.0.0 contact Matej Baran.
\n
\n3. USER AGREEMENT
\n
\n3.1 Use
\n
\nYour license to use BlueCapa 1.0.0 is limited to the number of licenses purchased by you. You shall not allow others to use, copy or evaluate copies of BlueCapa 1.0.0.
\n
\n3.2 Use Restrictions
\n
\nYou shall use BlueCapa 1.0.0 in compliance with all applicable laws and not for any unlawful purpose. Without limiting the foregoing, use, display or distribution of BlueCapa 1.0.0 together with material that is pornographic, racist, vulgar, obscene, defamatory, libelous, abusive, promoting hatred, discriminating or displaying prejudice based on religion, ethnic heritage, race, sexual orientation or age is strictly prohibited.
\n
\nEach licensed copy of BlueCapa 1.0.0 may be used on one single computer location by one user. Use of BlueCapa 1.0.0 means that you have loaded, installed, or run BlueCapa 1.0.0 on a computer or similar device. If you install BlueCapa 1.0.0 onto a multi-user platform, server or network, each and every individual user of BlueCapa 1.0.0 must be licensed separately.
\n
\nYou may make one copy of BlueCapa 1.0.0 for backup purposes, providing you only have one copy installed on one computer being used by one person. Other users may not use your copy of BlueCapa 1.0.0 . The assignment, sublicense, networking, sale, or distribution of copies of BlueCapa 1.0.0 are strictly forbidden without the prior written consent of Matej Baran. It is a violation of this agreement to assign, sell, share, loan, rent, lease, borrow, network or transfer the use of BlueCapa 1.0.0. If any person other than yourself uses BlueCapa 1.0.0 registered in your name, regardless of whether it is at the same time or different times, then this agreement is being violated and you are responsible for that violation!
\n
\n3.3 Copyright Restriction
\n
\nThis Software contains copyrighted material, trade secrets and other proprietary material. You shall not, and shall not attempt to, modify, reverse engineer, disassemble or decompile BlueCapa 1.0.0. Nor can you create any derivative works or other works that are based upon or derived from BlueCapa 1.0.0 in whole or in part.
\n
\nMatej Baran\'s name, logo and graphics file that represents BlueCapa 1.0.0 shall not be used in any way to promote products developed with BlueCapa 1.0.0 . Matej Baran retains sole and exclusive ownership of all right, title and interest in and to BlueCapa 1.0.0 and all Intellectual Property rights relating thereto.
\n
\nCopyright law and international copyright treaty provisions protect all parts of BlueCapa 1.0.0, products and services. No program, code, part, image, audio sample, or text may be copied or used in any way by the user except as intended within the bounds of the single user program. All rights not expressly granted hereunder are reserved for Matej Baran.
\n
\n3.4 Limitation of Responsibility
\n
\nYou will indemnify, hold harmless, and defend Matej Baran , its employees, agents and distributors against any and all claims, proceedings, demand and costs resulting from or in any way connected with your use of Matej Baran\'s Software.
\n
\nIn no event (including, without limitation, in the event of negligence) will Matej Baran , its employees, agents or distributors be liable for any consequential, incidental, indirect, special or punitive damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, loss of use, business interruption, loss of information or data, or pecuniary loss), in connection with or arising out of or related to this Agreement, BlueCapa 1.0.0 or the use or inability to use BlueCapa 1.0.0 or the furnishing, performance or use of any other matters hereunder whether based upon contract, tort or any other theory including negligence.
\n
\nMatej Baran\'s entire liability, without exception, is limited to the customers\' reimbursement of the purchase price of the Software (maximum being the lesser of the amount paid by you and the suggested retail price as listed by Matej Baran ) in exchange for the return of the product, all copies, registration papers and manuals, and all materials that constitute a transfer of license from the customer back to Matej Baran.
\n
\n3.5 Warranties
\n
\nExcept as expressly stated in writing, Matej Baran makes no representation or warranties in respect of this Software and expressly excludes all other warranties, expressed or implied, oral or written, including, without limitation, any implied warranties of merchantable quality or fitness for a particular purpose.
\n
\n3.6 Governing Law
\n
\nThis Agreement shall be governed by the law of the Slovakia applicable therein. You hereby irrevocably attorn and submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Slovakia therefrom. If any provision shall be considered unlawful, void or otherwise unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from this License and not affect the validity and enforceability of any other provisions.
\n
\n3.7 Termination
\n
\nAny failure to comply with the terms and conditions of this Agreement will result in automatic and immediate termination of this license. Upon termination of this license granted herein for any reason, you agree to immediately cease use of BlueCapa 1.0.0 and destroy all copies of BlueCapa 1.0.0 supplied under this Agreement. The financial obligations incurred by you shall survive the expiration or termination of this license.
\n
\n4. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY
\n
\nTHIS SOFTWARE AND THE ACCOMPANYING FILES ARE SOLD \"AS IS\" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES AS TO PERFORMANCE OR MERCHANTABILITY OR ANY OTHER WARRANTIES WHETHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED. THIS DISCLAIMER CONCERNS ALL FILES GENERATED AND EDITED BY BlueCapa 1.0.0 AS WELL.
\n
\n5. CONSENT OF USE OF DATA
\n
\nYou agree that Matej Baran may collect and use information gathered in any manner as part of the product support services provided to you, if any, related to BlueCapa 1.0.0.Matej Baran may also use this information to provide notices to you which may be of use or interest to you.
\n
    </string>
</resources>
